https://www.dltk-kids.com/privacy.htm

DLTK-Kids
Search
New 25
Top 10
DLTK's Inc. ("DLTK") is committed to protecting your privacy.
We have created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our
commitment to protecting the privacy of all of our users.
Google provides our Search Engine results (if you search our site) and our Advertising and our youTube videos. They use cookies (see the next section for what cookies are) on our websites when they provide these services.
For viewers in the EEA (European Economic Area), you will receive a message that allows you to choose between personalized or non-personalized ads. EEA visitors who want to revoke consent can click here for consent revocation.
Any viewers that are using ad blocking software will receive a message asking them to whitelist our site in order to continue. If you would prefer not to whitelist our site and allow ads you can subscribe to Contributor, a service that allows you to pay a nominal amount for each page you visit on our sites instead of allowing advertising. If you are a Contributor user and would like to remove our site from your removal pass please click here.
What the Heck are Cookies!?
On the internet... for some strange reason... someone decided to call certain text files "cookies" (sadly, they're not the yummy chocolate chip kind).
Internet Cookies are text files stored on your computer to collect visitor behaviour information.  This information is
used to track visitor use of the internet.
OK... that was a lot of big words. "The information in the cookies is used to track visitor use of the internet":
For example, if you go to lots of websites about cats, you might start seeing advertisements about cats and cat food and kitty litter. That's because "cookies" have been saved on your computer during your travels on the internet. An idea of what you've been interested in lately exists in those "cookies" files and smart computer programs read them to try to make the internet show you things the smart computer
programs think you'll enjoy.
The cookies are on your computer (or iPad or smartphone). We aren't storing them in some secret database somewhere. You are, heh. Or more accurately, your computer is.
Advertisers and search engines and social media sites/apps and youTube read those cookies to get an idea of what kind of things you like so they can serve you better (and, since they're businesses, so they can make more money).
Some internet users like this personalized internet experience (they get to see lots of ads and search engine results targetted specifically to them. If they like cats, they see lots of stuff about cats everywhere they go ... like
cute cat video suggestions when they visit youTube).
Other people find this all a bit creepy... maybe they don't want everyone to know they like cats or maybe they just don't quite trust what the information is being used for.
Now... as a mom, I actually like cookies
because
when I use the computer my daughters use I get a feel for what kind of stuff they've been looking at (I see lots of ads about cats). If I suddenly start seeing lots of ads about diet pills, I might decide to chat with the girls about how they're feeling about their bodies/weight/health.
For more information about cookies and how they're used visit https://cookiesandyou.com/.
You can set your browser not to accept cookies and the above websites tell you how to remove cookies from your browser.  Every device and browser you use will need to be set up this way if you want to stop cookies from being saved (your computer, your iPad, your smartphone) and if you're on a friend's computer or a computer at school, the cookies on that computer will likely be turned on.
What is Personal Information?
Personal information is information that identifies you as an
individual.  It includes information such as your name or email address.
Under no circumstances should you ever provide personal information such
as birth date, home address, school address, social insurance number (Canada), social
security number (U.S.) or financial information to someone claiming to
be from DLTK's.  We will NEVER request or have need of this
information.
If you're under 18 you shouldn't provide any personal information about yourself to anyone on the internet until you've sat down with your mom and / or dad (who I'm sure are really much hipper (more hip?) than you realize) and
lead them through a conversation about what you can and shouldn't share. Pro tip: write down your thoughts beforehand if you get flustered when you talk to your parents... we tend to listen better if you show us you've put some effort into getting us to just hush and hear you *wink*!
Talk to them before you share any info about yourself. Talk to them if you mess up and wish you hadn't shared something. Talk to them if you get cyberbullied. Talk to them if you have participated in cyberbullying and feel awful about it. Talk to them. They're on your team.
Information DLTK's Inc Collects
The information we may collect or obtain includes:
Your name,
Your email address and
Viewer ideas, photographs or drawings that you have
contributed.
And you'll never NEED to give us that info. If you'd like your name listed as the person who contributed an idea, drawing or photo we're happy to list you as contributor. But it's completely up to you. We're just as happy to list contributions as anonymous.
We only collect this info if you give it to us. We don't have some secret way to get it from you... if you're telling me your name, you'll know you're doing it!
DLTK does not collect personal information about you without your
knowledge and consent.
Personal Information Disclosure by DLTK
We will not disclose your personal information to third parties
without your consent to do so.
That sounds kind of weird and scary. What I mean is that if you send me a picture of a cat that you drew for the FanArt section and say "drawn by Sally, age 9" then I'll show the picture with the words "drawn by Sally, age 9" underneath of the picture.
I almost never show last names. I only
show last names if the person is a grown up and wants to keep copyright on the picture they drew or the photo they took. Then I list their last name and sometimes even their email address if they want me to though I try to discourage them from posting their email address on the internet because if you do, you end up getting lots of annoying junk mail.
Other Partners
There are a few features on the sites that we have offered
in conjunction with a third party because we do not have the
expertise to create these ourselves.  Because they are provided by
third parties we do not control the technical backbone so you may
wish to refer to the privacy policy of these third parties to be
sure you are comfortable with the way they may handle the
information you are providing.  Here are some links:
Java Jigsaw Puzzles by Jigzone.com
(Jigzone
Privacy Policy)
Ezoic (advertising Partner)
CLICK HERE TO CHANGE YOUR PRIVACY CONSENT SETTINGS
EZOIC SERVICE PRIVACY POLICY
dltk-kids.com ("Website") uses a third party technology called Ezoic.
INFORMATION ABOUT OUR ORGANIZATION AND WEBSITE
Ezoic is committed to protecting your privacy. We will only use the information that we collect lawfully in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (Regulation (EU) 2016/679).
Ezoic's principal activities are:
Website analytics
Website personalization
Website hosting
Our privacy policy covers Ezoic Inc., Ezoic Limited and this Website:
Ezoic Inc.
6023 Innovation Way, Carlsbad, California, United States
Ezoic Limited
Northern Design Centre, Abbott's Hill, Gateshead, NE8 3DF United Kingdom
DATA
In order to provide our products and services and related support, it is necessary for Ezoic to transfer your personal data outside of the European Union.  In such case, the data controller for this data for EU residents is Ezoic Inc. having it’s registered offices at 6023 Innovation Way, Carlsbad, California, United States.  All questions of requests regarding the processing of data may be addresses to data@ezoic.com
PROVIDING VISITORS WITH ANONYMOUS ACCESS
If you do not consent to such collection, you can access this website without disclosing your personal data.
AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF INFORMATION
Ezoic records data about the individuals and the traffic to this website. Ezoic is this website's limited agent (and data controller in the EU context) for the purpose of providing Internet data and optimization services. Ezoic may use this data to improve its service or enable other services (e.g., using visitor traffic logs or data posted through the service to improve the optimization of other websites).
Personal Information
Ezoic may collect personal information as defined in GDPR (such as IP address and a unique id in a cookie) about visitors to your website for the purposes of statistics, analytics and personalization. In addition, Ezoic works with numerous third parties for the collection and storage of data and the providing of analytics and advertising services.
Use of Personal Information
Purpose/Activity
Type(s) of Data
Lawful basis for processing
To improve user experience
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us to provide you with a more pleasant, efficient experience on this website that may be customized to how you or others respond to content and ads on this or other websites.
To improve ad performance
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us to optimize the placement, size, timing and number of ads displayed to you. It enables us to make smart decision that help this website owner earn money but reduce the disruption of ads on your experience.
To improve content creation
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us learn what content you care about and enjoy and, the style of content you like and what you engage the most with. This helps us produce more content and features that you might like.
To improve website performance
Identity
Technical
Usage
Your information helps us measure various performance metrics about our site, such as site speed, so that we can improve the performance of this site.
PROCESSING OF DATA AND CONSENT
We will process the data we collect about you to improve the operation of this and other websites. This information helps us make decisions about what content to show, how it should be formatted, the number, size and placement of advertisements and how content should be delivered to individuals. THis information is also used for analysis of performance and reporting.
USE OF APPLICATION LOGS
Our servers automatically record information (“Application Log Data”) created by your use of this website. Application Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We use this information to diagnose and improve our services. Except as stated in section (Data Retention), we will either delete the Application Log Data or remove any account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 48 months.
DATA RETENTION
The personal information we collect is retained for no longer than necessary to fulfil the stated purposes in section “PROCESSING OF DATA AND CONSENT” above or for a period specifically required by law or regulation that Ezoic is obligated to follow. Personal data used to fulfil verification of certain types of services such as SSL certificate, payments, and billing will be retained for a minimum of 5 years depending on the class of product or service and may be retained in either a physical or electronic format. Even if you request deletion or erasure of your data, we may retain your personal data to the extent necessary and for so long as necessary for our legitimate business interests or performance of contractual obligations. After the retention period is over, Ezoic securely disposes or anonymizes your personal information in order to prevent loss, theft, misuse, or unauthorized access.
CONFIDENTIALITY / SECURITY
We have implemented security policies, rules and technical measures to protect the personal data that we have under our control from: unauthorized access improper use or disclosure unauthorized modification unlawful destruction or accidental loss. All our employees and data processors, who have access to, and are associated with the processing of personal data, are obliged to respect the confidentiality of our visitors’ personal data. We ensure that your personal data will not be disclosed to State institutions and authorities except if required by law or other regulation
DATA ACCESS & DELETION
You have the right to view information that we have collected about you and to request deletion of any personal information we may have. You can use this data lookup tool to complete these actions.
Below is a list of cookies that are commonly set on this website.
Below is a list of usage, technical and identify metrics that are commonly stored and processed when you use this website
Your location information, including country, state, city, metro and postal code
The webpage your were at before this website
The type of browser you use and the version
The brand and operating system of your device
What time zone you're in and what time it is there
What pages on this site you visit
How you interact with this website, including time spent, how much you scroll and your mouse movements
The size of your devices screen and the size of the browser on that screen
What content you share on the page
If you copy and paste content on this website
What ad or link you clicked on to arrive at this website
The type of internet connection you use and your ISP or service provider
How long it takes for this website's content to get transfered to your browser, load in your browser and render
The weather where you are currently located
Your age and gender
Your ip address
A unique id so that we can recognize you
What ads you click on
Cookies
Cookie NameCategoryDescriptionDuration_1ci_7ag23o86kjasbfdUnclassifiedfpcidUnclassifiedCNZZDATA#UnclassifiedASPSESSIONIDNecessaryPreserves users states across page requests.ezovuuidtime_#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the time of your visit to this website so different visits can be differentiated from each other.2880 minezovuuid_#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify a visit by you to this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.30 minactive_template::#NecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store which template you are viewing on this website.ez_pub_siteNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to only show the site with Ezoic's features enabled. ezCMPCookieConsentNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track when a user consents to cookies.ez_rdr_countNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track redirectsez_rdrNecessaryUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track redirects.session_depthNecessaryUsed to track the number of pages you visit in a session on this site._dc_gtm_UA-#NecessaryUsed by Google Tag Manager to load other scripts and code on the page.BCSI-CS-#NecessaryUsed by networks with Bluecoat technology proxy servers to identify users.cookieconsent_dismissedNecessaryUsed to track closure of a cookie consent dialog.__utmt_eNecessaryUsed to throttle the speed of requests to the server.__utmt_fNecessaryUsed to throttle the speed of requests to the server.ez_view_original_onlyPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the original site without Ezoic's features.ez_view_optimized_onlyPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the optimized site with Ezoic's features.ez_view_optimized_only
PreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to show the original site without Ezoic's features.speed_no_processPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to turn off site speed features for this user.sitespeed_previewPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to allow this user to preview certain site speed features.ez_ad_position_versionPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to determine if they use the Ad Tester product for this user, used by the Ad Tester extension.ezpicker_showallPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to tell the ezpicker app to show all placeholders.ezpicker_nocachePreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to tell the ezpicker app to run without using the cache.ezpickerPreferencesUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to turn on ezpickerGED_PLAYLIST_ACTIVITYPreferencesUsed to track activity related to embeded YoutTube videosSL_GWPT_Show_Hide_tmpPreferencesSL_wptGlobTipTmpPreferencesezuz_ifep_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record whether you have engaged with the content on this site.
Used for analytics purposes to improve user experience.ezux_et_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the amount of time that you engaged with content on this website. Used for analytics purposes to improve user experience._gat_gtag_UA_#StatisticsUsed by Google Analytics for user tracking.__qcaStatisticsCollects anonymous data on the user's visits to the website, such as the number of visits, average time spent on the website and what pages have been loaded with the purpose of generating reports for optimising the website content.ezux_tos_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the amount of time you have spent on this website.ezoadgid_#StatisticsRecords an id that to your age and gender category.
For example, id 923 might be for males between 20 and 30 years old.30 minezoab_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to split test different features and functionality.120 minezCMPCCSStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track when a user consents to statistics cookies._gaStatisticsUsed to distinguish users by Google Analyticsezopvc_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the number of pages that you have viewed on this site in this session.30 min_gidStatisticsUsed to distinguish users by Google Analyticsezoref_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the referring domain (the website you were at before you can to this website).120 minezux_lpl_#Statistics Used by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to record the time that you loaded the last page on this website.ezutm_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the list of utm parameters that they have access to.ezosuigeneriscStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you across different websites on the internet so your experience can be customized.ezoawesome_#Statistics Used by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, for fraud and invalid activity detection.ezovid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify a visit by you to this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.ezouid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you as a visitor on this website. Used for analytics and personalization of your experience.ezosuigenerisStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to uniquely identify you across different websites on the internet so your experience can be customized.ezostid_#StatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to test different features and functionality and to record which features and functionality are available to you so you receive a consistent experience.ezdsStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the pixel size of your screen to help personalize your experience and ensure content fits.ez_recommended_pagesStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track users visiting from the recommended pages widget.AMP_ECID_EZOICStatisticsUsed by personalization and analytics company Ezoic for statistics on Accelerated Mobile PagesezouspvvStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited.ezouspvhStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited since their last visit.ezouspvaStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track how many pages a user has visited all time.ezepvvStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to track which pages this user has viewed.ezohwStatisticsUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store the pixel size of your browser to help personalize your experience and ensure content fits.__utmbStatisticsRegisters a timestamp with the exact time of when the user accessed the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit.__utmzStatisticsCollects data on where the user came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked and what search term was used. Used by Google Analytics.__utmaStatisticsCollects data on the number of times a user has visited the website as well as dates for the first and most recent visit. Used by Google Analytics.__utmcStatisticsRegisters a timestamp with the exact time of when the user leaves the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit.__utmvStatisticsUsed to store visitor-level custom variable data in Google Analytics.__utmdStatisticsUsed by Google Analytics to track your activity on a website._gatStatisticsUsed to distinguish users by Google Analytics_pk_ses..#StatisticsUsed by Matomo (Piwik) for analytics tracking._pk_id..#StatisticsUsed by Matomo (Piwik) for analytics tracking, storing a unique visitor ID.__gadsMarketingUsed to register what ads have been displayed to the user.ezdgMarketingUsed by the analytics and personalization company, Ezoic, to store demographic information like age and gender.180 minOX_plgMarketingUsed by ad network OpenX to identify a user across multiple websitesmindsparktb_#MarketingUsed by advertising company Mindspark to identify users._sm_auMarketingUsed by Google Adwords to retarget ads to users.cto_optoutMarketingUsed by ad network Criteo to record if you've opted of personalized ads._ym_uidMarketingUsed by Ad Company Yandex Metrica to identify users.SSM_GFUMarketingUsed by ad personalization company SpeedShiftMedia to track your browsing activity and how many ads have been displayed to you.SSM_UTC_LSMarketingUsed by ad personalization company SpeedShiftMedia to track your browsing activity and how many ads have been displayed to you.SSM_UTCMarketingUsed by ad personalization company SpeedShiftMedia to track your browsing activity and how many ads have been displayed to you.
A list of Vendors that may be used on this website
Data Usage Purposes
Necessary
Necessary cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies.
Preferences
Preference cookies enable a website to remember information that changes the way the website behaves or looks, like your preferred language or the region that you are in.
Statistics
Statistic cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously.
Marketing
Marketing cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers.
Contacting Us If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy or you wish to unsubscribe from our site and services you may contact us using the information below or by writing to us at:
2885 Sanford Ave
Grandville, MI 49418
USA
Summary of Requests If you'd like to see a summary of the requests to know user information, requests to delete user information and requests to opt-out of ccpa compliance that this business has received:
https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/dltk-kids.com/annualRequestSummary
regarding dltk-kids.com
Email:
More Legal Stuff
DLTK's Inc. is a Canadian company run by a mom and a dad from Alberta, Canada (near the Rocky Mountains). Our daughters help us sometimes... mostly they ignore us, heh. We don't have employees so if someone contacts you claiming to be from our company, they're lying. I wish people didn't lie but sometimes they do. If you're young and you aren't sure if someone is lying to you, talk to your parents about it. If something seems too good to be true, it's likely a lie.
This Privacy Policy is intended to comply with the Canadian federal
government’s privacy legislation, the Personal Information Protection
and Electronic Documents Act, as well as Alberta’s Personal Information
Protection Act.  We want you to understand how and under what
circumstances your personal information is collected, used and
disclosed, as well as what DLTK's is doing to ensure that your information
is used according to good business practices and is protected
accordingly.
Contacting DLTK's
If you have any requests, questions or comments about your personal
information or this Privacy Policy, you may contact us by email: webmaster@dltk-kids.com.
This Privacy Policy may be changed from time to time without notice.
Revisions will be posted on DLTK's website.  This
Privacy Policy is dated June 1, 2018.
Thank you for visiting DLTK's Sites!
x
x
